{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958526431","data":{"timestamp":" 946958526431"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958548970","data":{"timestamp":" 946958548969"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958566727","data":{"timestamp":" 946958566727"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" be64fea0-6328-4ce5-8b5d-fa2a85cab209"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958618574","data":{"timestamp":" 946958618573"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" be64fea0-6328-4ce5-8b5d-fa2a85cab209"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958618710","data":{"timestamp":" 946958618710"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" be64fea0-6328-4ce5-8b5d-fa2a85cab209"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958715984","data":{"timestamp":" 946958715983"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" be64fea0-6328-4ce5-8b5d-fa2a85cab209"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958770560","data":{"timestamp":" 946958770560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" a113bdb0-dd97-4f58-91ed-40b0bd810ca9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958819417","data":{"timestamp":" 946958819415"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" a113bdb0-dd97-4f58-91ed-40b0bd810ca9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958819544","data":{"timestamp":" 946958819544"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" a113bdb0-dd97-4f58-91ed-40b0bd810ca9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958859389","data":{"timestamp":" 946958859388"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958862012","data":{"timestamp":" 946958862011"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" START_SABUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958864812","data":{"timestamp":" 946958864812"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958866421","data":{"timestamp":" 946958866420"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958872085","data":{"timestamp":" 946958872085"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958873690","data":{"timestamp":" 946958873689"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958876739","data":{"timestamp":" 946958876739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958878338","data":{"timestamp":" 946958878337"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958886172","data":{"timestamp":" 946958886172"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958887824","data":{"timestamp":" 946958887824"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958890712","data":{"timestamp":" 946958890712"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958892269","data":{"timestamp":" 946958892269"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958895487","data":{"timestamp":" 946958895486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958897123","data":{"timestamp":" 946958897122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958899984","data":{"timestamp":" 946958899984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958901608","data":{"timestamp":" 946958901607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958904496","data":{"timestamp":" 946958904495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958906129","data":{"timestamp":" 946958906128"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958908728","data":{"timestamp":" 946958908728"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958910357","data":{"timestamp":" 946958910356"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958912948","data":{"timestamp":" 946958912947"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958914563","data":{"timestamp":" 946958914562"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958917631","data":{"timestamp":" 946958917630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958919661","data":{"timestamp":" 946958919659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958919749","data":{"timestamp":" 946958919749"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 123bb0af-a3ef-4fda-81d6-e782ec6b709b"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958936525","data":{"timestamp":" 946958936524"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" SABUNI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958942797","data":{"timestamp":" 946958942796"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" START_SABUNI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958945866","data":{"timestamp":" 946958945866"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SABUNI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SABUNI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958947489","data":{"timestamp":" 946958947488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958952107","data":{"timestamp":" 946958952107"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAHANI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAHANI"," userResponse":" SAHANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958953726","data":{"timestamp":" 946958953725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958956600","data":{"timestamp":" 946958956599"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" START_SUFURIA"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958960109","data":{"timestamp":" 946958960108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUFURIA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUFURIA"," userResponse":" SUFURIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958961713","data":{"timestamp":" 946958961713"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958965325","data":{"timestamp":" 946958965324"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAMAKI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAMAKI"," userResponse":" SAMAKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958966945","data":{"timestamp":" 946958966944"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958970074","data":{"timestamp":" 946958970073"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMAMA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMAMA"," userResponse":" SIMAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958971699","data":{"timestamp":" 946958971698"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958974953","data":{"timestamp":" 946958974953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SHANGAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SHANGAZI"," userResponse":" SHANGAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958976559","data":{"timestamp":" 946958976558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958979756","data":{"timestamp":" 946958979756"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SUNGURA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SUNGURA"," userResponse":" SUNGURA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958981374","data":{"timestamp":" 946958981373"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958984291","data":{"timestamp":" 946958984291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIKIO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958985885","data":{"timestamp":" 946958985885"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958988496","data":{"timestamp":" 946958988495"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SWALA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SWALA"," userResponse":" SWALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958990131","data":{"timestamp":" 946958990130"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958992689","data":{"timestamp":" 946958992688"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SAA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SAA"," userResponse":" SAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958994306","data":{"timestamp":" 946958994305"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958996895","data":{"timestamp":" 946958996895"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-S.rand.33","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958998926","data":{"timestamp":" 946958998924"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946958999039","data":{"timestamp":" 946958999039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959076957","data":{"timestamp":" 946959076956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5ed72ccb-fc21-4b3d-ac39-3f50f3bde7ed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-S.rand.33"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" SIMBA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959098467","data":{"timestamp":" 946959098467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_D-S-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959102310","data":{"timestamp":" 946959102310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-S-B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959109810","data":{"timestamp":" 946959109810"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-I-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959113272","data":{"timestamp":" 946959113272"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_F-G-S"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959116621","data":{"timestamp":" 946959116620"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-I-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959120063","data":{"timestamp":" 946959120063"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-B-S"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959124437","data":{"timestamp":" 946959124437"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_D-S-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959130238","data":{"timestamp":" 946959130238"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_D-S-F"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959133724","data":{"timestamp":" 946959133724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_S-N-E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959137151","data":{"timestamp":" 946959137151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_W-T-S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959140764","data":{"timestamp":" 946959140763"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_U-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959146562","data":{"timestamp":" 946959146559"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 6f15f5b2-5817-4da9-8f97-c7f51f53d6d8"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.show.61"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_S_U-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959165815","data":{"timestamp":" 946959165815"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-S-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959171203","data":{"timestamp":" 946959171203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_M-S-R"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959176941","data":{"timestamp":" 946959176941"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_N-S-Y"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959180566","data":{"timestamp":" 946959180566"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_S-V-E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959184352","data":{"timestamp":" 946959184352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_F-G-S"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959189033","data":{"timestamp":" 946959189033"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-F-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959194498","data":{"timestamp":" 946959194498"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-F-S"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959199154","data":{"timestamp":" 946959199154"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_E-S-Z"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959202718","data":{"timestamp":" 946959202718"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_CH-P-S"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959206743","data":{"timestamp":" 946959206743"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_V-E-S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959210427","data":{"timestamp":" 946959210427"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_T-F-S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959214333","data":{"timestamp":" 946959214333"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-S-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959220147","data":{"timestamp":" 946959220147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 64c54158-b9cb-42cf-bdf8-44d6e1d721fc"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_S..S.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.62"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_S_J-S-B"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959242907","data":{"timestamp":" 946959242906"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_U_K"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959249546","data":{"timestamp":" 946959249545"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_J_A_S"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959256186","data":{"timestamp":" 946959256186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_B_S_E"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959262823","data":{"timestamp":" 946959262823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_H_T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959270299","data":{"timestamp":" 946959270298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_H_T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959276952","data":{"timestamp":" 946959276951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Y_S_A"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959283621","data":{"timestamp":" 946959283621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_S_I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959290282","data":{"timestamp":" 946959290282"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_D_U"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959296962","data":{"timestamp":" 946959296961"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_T_H_S"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959303617","data":{"timestamp":" 946959303617"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_V_S"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959310281","data":{"timestamp":" 946959310281"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_S_H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:S..S.all.10.rand.say.32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959322355","data":{"timestamp":" 946959322355"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" b4e0749c-822e-4078-a1b9-5bd5e361b8ac"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_S..S.all.10.rand.say.32"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_R_S_H"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959336430","data":{"timestamp":" 946959336430"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959339228","data":{"timestamp":" 946959339228"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959340842","data":{"timestamp":" 946959340841"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959343128","data":{"timestamp":" 946959343127"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959344730","data":{"timestamp":" 946959344729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959347007","data":{"timestamp":" 946959347006"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" CH"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959348608","data":{"timestamp":" 946959348607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959350760","data":{"timestamp":" 946959350760"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959352370","data":{"timestamp":" 946959352369"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959354561","data":{"timestamp":" 946959354560"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959356158","data":{"timestamp":" 946959356157"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959361792","data":{"timestamp":" 946959361790"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959363390","data":{"timestamp":" 946959363389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959366478","data":{"timestamp":" 946959366478"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959368085","data":{"timestamp":" 946959368084"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959374985","data":{"timestamp":" 946959374984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959376598","data":{"timestamp":" 946959376597"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959379103","data":{"timestamp":" 946959379103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959380705","data":{"timestamp":" 946959380705"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959383067","data":{"timestamp":" 946959383067"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959384672","data":{"timestamp":" 946959384671"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959387380","data":{"timestamp":" 946959387379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959388993","data":{"timestamp":" 946959388992"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959391510","data":{"timestamp":" 946959391509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959393125","data":{"timestamp":" 946959393125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959395911","data":{"timestamp":" 946959395911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959397522","data":{"timestamp":" 946959397521"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959400103","data":{"timestamp":" 946959400102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959401704","data":{"timestamp":" 946959401703"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959406957","data":{"timestamp":" 946959406956"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959408558","data":{"timestamp":" 946959408558"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959412589","data":{"timestamp":" 946959412589"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959414190","data":{"timestamp":" 946959414189"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959418822","data":{"timestamp":" 946959418822"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959420379","data":{"timestamp":" 946959420379"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959425106","data":{"timestamp":" 946959425106"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959426715","data":{"timestamp":" 946959426714"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959430595","data":{"timestamp":" 946959430594"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959432197","data":{"timestamp":" 946959432197"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959434607","data":{"timestamp":" 946959434607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959436211","data":{"timestamp":" 946959436210"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959438739","data":{"timestamp":" 946959438739"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959440358","data":{"timestamp":" 946959440357"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959442450","data":{"timestamp":" 946959442449"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959444044","data":{"timestamp":" 946959444043"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959446279","data":{"timestamp":" 946959446278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959447912","data":{"timestamp":" 946959447911"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959450479","data":{"timestamp":" 946959450479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959452514","data":{"timestamp":" 946959452513"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959452619","data":{"timestamp":" 946959452619"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_18","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959475622","data":{"timestamp":" 946959475621"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 9d2a2c5f-461e-45b5-b810-a8ce61ffc043"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__all.A..Z.asc.uc.3__it_18"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959500122","data":{"timestamp":" 946959500122"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5c9c2691-ec8c-4402-baa0-5b3e2a2ecd18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959552748","data":{"timestamp":" 946959552747"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5c9c2691-ec8c-4402-baa0-5b3e2a2ecd18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"946959552903","data":{"timestamp":" 946959552903"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000104_070155"," gameId":" 5c9c2691-ec8c-4402-baa0-5b3e2a2ecd18"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"end":"end"}]}